[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "Good to be with you.", "answer_tokens": ["Good", "to", "be", "with", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "If he's reunited the whole of America, including you, this is a good step forward, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["If", "he", "'s", "reunited", "the", "whole", "of", "America", ",", "including", "you", ",", "this", "is", "a", "good", "step", "forward", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "That's right.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "Do you think they should live up to their rhetoric?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "they", "should", "live", "up", "to", "their", "rhetoric", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "TO", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "Well, ideally, sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "ideally", ",", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joe Biden"]}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "So by his own words, he is no longer qualified to be president, is he, Mr. Speaker?", "question_tokens": ["So", "by", "his", "own", "words", ",", "he", "is", "no", "longer", "qualified", "to", "be", "president", ",", "is", "he", ",", "Mr.", "Speaker", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "Well, if we're going to apply that standard, Joe Biden has to resign this evening because he has said enough different goofy things over time that you couldn't possibly remain vice president.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "if", "we", "'re", "going", "to", "apply", "that", "standard", ",", "Joe", "Biden", "has", "to", "resign", "this", "evening", "because", "he", "has", "said", "enough", "different", "goofy", "things", "over", "time", "that", "you", "could", "n't", "possibly", "remain", "vice", "president", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Speaker"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "But if he's going to seal the deal, Mitt Romney, and actually win this election, what's he got to do now?", "question_tokens": ["But", "if", "he", "'s", "going", "to", "seal", "the", "deal", ",", "Mitt", "Romney", ",", "and", "actually", "win", "this", "election", ",", "what", "'s", "he", "got", "to", "do", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "I think he's got to do two things and I think they're pretty clear but pretty hard.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "'s", "got", "to", "do", "two", "things", "and", "I", "think", "they", "'re", "pretty", "clear", "but", "pretty", "hard", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "That must be a failure by the Romney campaign, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "must", "be", "a", "failure", "by", "the", "Romney", "campaign", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "Governor, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Governor", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "Well, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "How about you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "about", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "Very well.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "How are you reacting to Mitt Romney's tax returns which have landed this Friday afternoon?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "reacting", "to", "Mitt", "Romney", "'s", "tax", "returns", "which", "have", "landed", "this", "Friday", "afternoon", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "Well, I think it's about time but it's really only part of the story.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "about", "time", "but", "it", "'s", "really", "only", "part", "of", "the", "story", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Friday"], "PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"], "TIME": ["afternoon"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 121, "question": "Absolutely staggering amount, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Absolutely", "staggering", "amount", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBG", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 122, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "What do you mean by that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "mean", "by", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Cayman Island"]}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "JJS", "NNPS", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "Is there anything ethically wrong with what he's been doing?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "anything", "ethically", "wrong", "with", "what", "he", "'s", "been", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "I think the bigger issue about the failure to release his tax returns, he must know that most Americans would react with some horror at the degree to which he's used tax avoidance schemes and Cayman Island bank accounts and the like to avoid paying the full amount of taxes that he should.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "bigger", "issue", "about", "the", "failure", "to", "release", "his", "tax", "returns", ",", "he", "must", "know", "that", "most", "Americans", "would", "react", "with", "some", "horror", "at", "the", "degree", "to", "which", "he", "'s", "used", "tax", "avoidance", "schemes", "and", "Cayman", "Island", "bank", "accounts", "and", "the", "like", "to", "avoid", "paying", "the", "full", "amount", "of", "taxes", "that", "he", "should", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "It seems to me just looking at them, anyone that gives $4 million to charity in one year, you can hardly accuse him of milking the system too much, can you?", "question_tokens": ["It", "seems", "to", "me", "just", "looking", "at", "them", ",", "anyone", "that", "gives", "$", "4", "million", "to", "charity", "in", "one", "year", ",", "you", "can", "hardly", "accuse", "him", "of", "milking", "the", "system", "too", "much", ",", "can", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "$", "CD", "CD", "TO", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "That's right.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$4 million"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "I mean, is that the bottom line?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "is", "that", "the", "bottom", "line", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "That's the real message when you dig into the tax returns that have been released, is the tremendous sophistication and expense required to effectively avoid taxes as well as he has.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "the", "real", "message", "when", "you", "dig", "into", "the", "tax", "returns", "that", "have", "been", "released", ",", "is", "the", "tremendous", "sophistication", "and", "expense", "required", "to", "effectively", "avoid", "taxes", "as", "well", "as", "he", "has", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Henry"]}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "Henry Rosen, what do you make of this?", "question_tokens": ["Henry", "Rosen", ",", "what", "do", "you", "make", "of", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "I think Henry's right.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "Henry", "'s", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Henry Rosen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Harry Reid", "Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 215, "question": "Doesn't Harry Reid have to stand up now and issue a public apology to Mitt Romney?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "n't", "Harry", "Reid", "have", "to", "stand", "up", "now", "and", "issue", "a", "public", "apology", "to", "Mitt", "Romney", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "RB", "CC", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 216, "answer": "My guess is Harry Reid would feel better if he actually saw the returns instead of a letter from a bunch of accountants swearing that Mitt Romney paid taxes.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "guess", "is", "Harry", "Reid", "would", "feel", "better", "if", "he", "actually", "saw", "the", "returns", "instead", "of", "a", "letter", "from", "a", "bunch", "of", "accountants", "swearing", "that", "Mitt", "Romney", "paid", "taxes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Harry Reid", "Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 217, "question": "You're saying the accountants are lying?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "saying", "the", "accountants", "are", "lying", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "So how do you think this plays out for the election?", "question_tokens": ["So", "how", "do", "you", "think", "this", "plays", "out", "for", "the", "election", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "Well, I think his entire economic plan has been based on the idea that we have to give more money to the job creators, the investors and the entrepreneurs.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "his", "entire", "economic", "plan", "has", "been", "based", "on", "the", "idea", "that", "we", "have", "to", "give", "more", "money", "to", "the", "job", "creators", ",", "the", "investors", "and", "the", "entrepreneurs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "Do you ever wish that Mitt Romney was worth about 300 million less, that he was like a regular guy with a regular income, maybe worth three million dollars?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "ever", "wish", "that", "Mitt", "Romney", "was", "worth", "about", "300", "million", "less", ",", "that", "he", "was", "like", "a", "regular", "guy", "with", "a", "regular", "income", ",", "maybe", "worth", "three", "million", "dollars", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "CD", "CD", "JJR", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "JJ", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["three million dollars"], "PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "Are you or are you not?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "or", "are", "you", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "That's a lot to assume.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "lot", "to", "assume", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "Where do you get off?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "do", "you", "get", "off", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "Let me ask you a direct question.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "me", "ask", "you", "a", "direct", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "IN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "Are you or have you ever been a liberal?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "or", "have", "you", "ever", "been", "a", "liberal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "I don't know what that is.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "what", "that", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "Are you a conservative?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "a", "conservative", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "Yes, I'm a conservative.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "'m", "a", "conservative", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kenny"]}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "Would you categorize him as more of a liberal?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "categorize", "him", "as", "more", "of", "a", "liberal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "I would categorize Kenny as an independent actually.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "categorize", "Kenny", "as", "an", "independent", "actually", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "Do you vote?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "vote", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", ",", "DT", "CD", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "MD", "VB", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 355, "question": "Who do you vote for normally?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "do", "you", "vote", "for", "normally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "I have always voted for the best person, the one that moved me, that I felt would inspire me, would inspire everything else around me.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "always", "voted", "for", "the", "best", "person", ",", "the", "one", "that", "moved", "me", ",", "that", "I", "felt", "would", "inspire", "me", ",", "would", "inspire", "everything", "else", "around", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Morgan"]}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CC", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "NNP", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "Why do I feel I'm losing control of this interview?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "I", "feel", "I", "'m", "losing", "control", "of", "this", "interview", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "Ladies and gentlemen, piers Morgan receives a hug.", "answer_tokens": ["Ladies", "and", "gentlemen", ",", "piers", "Morgan", "receives", "a", "hug", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "My God, is that the first time anyone's hugged you in your life?", "question_tokens": ["My", "God", ",", "is", "that", "the", "first", "time", "anyone", "'s", "hugged", "you", "in", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "Is it time for a commercial break, he cries out desperately.", "answer_tokens": ["Is", "it", "time", "for", "a", "commercial", "break", ",", "he", "cries", "out", "desperately", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "CD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 371, "question": "Parking who you actually vote for to one side, what are the issues that you really are divided over, would you say?", "question_tokens": ["Parking", "who", "you", "actually", "vote", "for", "to", "one", "side", ",", "what", "are", "the", "issues", "that", "you", "really", "are", "divided", "over", ",", "would", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "CD", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 372, "answer": "I can tell you the issues that -- we tour like crazy, 60 some odd cities this year, all over the United States.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "can", "tell", "you", "the", "issues", "that", "--", "we", "tour", "like", "crazy", ",", "60", "some", "odd", "cities", "this", "year", ",", "all", "over", "the", "United", "States", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "You going to outlaw alcohol and cars?", "question_tokens": ["You", "going", "to", "outlaw", "alcohol", "and", "cars", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "I find that a fatuous argument.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "find", "that", "a", "fatuous", "argument", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "ORGAN: You would shoot them dead?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "You", "would", "shoot", "them", "dead", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "DT", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "You know what a hillbilly is, Piers?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "what", "a", "hillbilly", "is", ",", "Piers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "DT", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "I know what a hillbilly is.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "know", "what", "a", "hillbilly", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "Something that's dogged you for years afterward?", "question_tokens": ["Something", "that", "'s", "dogged", "you", "for", "years", "afterward", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "I did when it came out, sure, because I remember where I was when I heard the term the first time.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "when", "it", "came", "out", ",", "sure", ",", "because", "I", "remember", "where", "I", "was", "when", "I", "heard", "the", "term", "the", "first", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["weekend"]}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 470, "question": "Did you ever make up with Rob Lowe, like the old -- like Dean, Sammy, Frank, you all hang out together?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "make", "up", "with", "Rob", "Lowe", ",", "like", "the", "old", "--", "like", "Dean", ",", "Sammy", ",", "Frank", ",", "you", "all", "hang", "out", "together", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ":", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "Go to Vegas for the weekend, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Go", "to", "Vegas", "for", "the", "weekend", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rob Lowe", "Frank"], "LOCATION": ["Sammy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie Sheen"]}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 483, "question": "You ever party with Charlie Sheen?", "question_tokens": ["You", "ever", "party", "with", "Charlie", "Sheen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 484, "answer": "I never met Charlie Sheen.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "never", "met", "Charlie", "Sheen", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie Sheen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 501, "question": "What drives you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "drives", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "Well, it first started happening as a reaction to all that stuff you were just talking about.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "first", "started", "happening", "as", "a", "reaction", "to", "all", "that", "stuff", "you", "were", "just", "talking", "about", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RBR", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "RBR", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "Did it change your perspective of America too?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "it", "change", "your", "perspective", "of", "America", "too", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "The more I traveled the world, the more I realized America is a great place.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "more", "I", "traveled", "the", "world", ",", "the", "more", "I", "realized", "America", "is", "a", "great", "place", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "IN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "What was that all about?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "that", "all", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "Look, come on, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "come", "on", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "What did you learn about yourself in reality?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "learn", "about", "yourself", "in", "reality", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "I learned that you can't really reconcile the two.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "learned", "that", "you", "ca", "n't", "really", "reconcile", "the", "two", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 548, "question": "But do you to complete strangers in Patagonia?", "question_tokens": ["But", "do", "you", "to", "complete", "strangers", "in", "Patagonia", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Patagonia"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Jesus"]}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "Wake up every morning and say, is he still here?", "question_tokens": ["Wake", "up", "every", "morning", "and", "say", ",", "is", "he", "still", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "Look, I come back from some trips and she goes, Jesus, we're just getting the rhythm.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "I", "come", "back", "from", "some", "trips", "and", "she", "goes", ",", "Jesus", ",", "we", "'re", "just", "getting", "the", "rhythm", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120921pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 561, "question": "Does she accept you are just a nomad, that's the way you're going to be?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "she", "accept", "you", "are", "just", "a", "nomad", ",", "that", "'s", "the", "way", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 562, "answer": "Yeah, I think to a large degree.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "I", "think", "to", "a", "large", "degree", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]